tronsoundtrack.com 2015-11-21

# Privacy Policy – Domain Names for Generation XYZ®

We respect your privacy. XYZ® has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to you, our customer. This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for this website, xyz.xyz (the "Website”, "Us”, "Our”). By using the Website you agree to the privacy practices disclosed below.

## Privacy Practices

  * We do not give third parties access to your personal information other than as outlined in this privacy policy.
  * We only send email to you if you have elected to receive it.
  * If we determine that any account with us is being used for the purpose of sending spam or engaging in malicious activities, we will take action to shut it down as soon as possible.

We will never give any information about you to others without your express permission. Our site uses forms in which you give us contact information (like your name, address, phone number, and email address) so you can create an account, place orders, request information, etc. We may share specific information with business partners or contractors when the information is needed to fulfill your request for a product or service. We also use your contact information when it will be important for us to contact you regarding functionality changes to our products, our website, new services and special offers we think you’ll find valuable, and provide customer service.

We use information gathered about you from our site statistics via log files provided by third party tracking partners (for example your IP address) to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. We also gather broad demographic information from this data to help us improve our site and your experience. This information collection is not linked to any personally identifiable information. Our site uses cookies to keep track of your session information and to provide you with customized information. We do link the information we store in cookies to personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided by your internet browser (ex: Mozilla Firefox or Internet Explorer).

We also may use cookies to store your username if you request to remember your username during login. That information will be used to pre-fill the login form at a later time. If you are referred to our website through an ad or a partner, we will store the referral information in the cookies.
